Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events
1834-2025
New York University Archives
New York University. Office of University Events
New York University. Office of External Affairs. Commencement and Special Events
RG.7.4
96 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 59 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 flat box, 5 oversize flat boxes, 1 custom box, 1 flat-file folder, 8 folders in shared boxes, and 37 boxes without container profiles.
58 audiocassettes
26.7 Megabytes in 29 computer files
The New York University Commencement and Special Events division was part of the Office of External Affairs which operated under the leadership of the Vice President for External Affairs. In 2002, the Office of External Affairs was replaced by the Office of University Relations and Public Affairs, while the Office of University Events took over the role of event planning. This collection contains files created by these offices for University-wide and individual New York University school events dating from 1834 to 2019. Event planning files contain correspondence, notes, audio recordings, ephemera, and published material created for these events. This collection also contains a large assemblage of All-University Commencement programs, tickets, invitations, speeches, rosters, and plannings notes dating from 1834 to 2025. Baccalaureate service programs and other Commencement-related events ephemera are also in this collection. Files created for various Commencement financial prizes and awards document their creation and administration, dating from 1941 to 2000.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were first accessioned from the Office of External Affairs by the University Archives in 1997. Additional boxes were accessioned from the Office of University Events in 2011. Accretions were transferred to the Archives in 2016, 2018, 2019, 2022, 2024, and 2025.
Appraisal
Eight school banners, eleven audiocassettes, and two cartons of books previously owned by former University President John Brademas were removed and returned to the University Archivist.
Arrangement
Organized into four series: Series I. Events; Series II: Publications; Series III. Commencement; and Series IV. Commencement Prizes and Awards.
Series I and III are arranged chronologically, and in Series II the same events are grouped together and arranged chronologically within those groups. Series IV is arranged alphabetically.
Historical Note
The Commencement and Special Events division was part of the Office of External Affairs and operated under the direction of the Vice President for External Affairs. The Commencement and Special Events department was responsible for the planning, organization, and overseeing of university events and commencement ceremonies. Other than convocation ceremonies, the department regularly organized university events such as anniversary celebrations, guest lectures, fundraising dinners, and site dedications. In 2002, the Office of External Affairs was replaced by the Office of University Relations and Public Affairs. The Office of University Events operates within this division and coordinates the many events formerly handled by the Commencement and Special Events department of the Office of External Affairs.
Related Materials
Records of Arthur L. Brandon, 1957-1962
Records of the Office of Radio and Television, 1953-1985
Records of the Office of the Senior Vice President, William F. Payne, for External Affairs, 1968-1980
Scope and Contents
This collection contains planning files, publications, and ephemera generated by the Commencement and Special Events division of the Office of External Affairs, and the Office of University Events. Event planning files date from 1870 to 2019, documenting preparation for New York University events which includes lectures, faculty convocations, honorary degrees, NYU Presidential Inaugurations, and NYU's Sesquicentennial celebration (1980) activities. Published material in this collection includes programs and ephemera from 1956 to 1995 related to NYU events such as dedications, convocations, lectures, and building openings. These materials complement event files in Series I. Commencement files document the experience of attendees through ephemera, graduation rosters, speeches, audio recordings, event scripts, and planning notes for the Commencement ceremony itself and related events dating from 1834 to 2025. Files accumulated on prizes and awards in this collection typically contain correspondence and supporting documentation on financial awards distributed to individuals during Commencement week. These files date from 1941 to 2000.
Separated Materials
Oversized materials from the NYU Celebrates 2000 event were incorporated into general University Archives collections created for specific formats.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Programs (documents); New York (N.Y.).; Correspondence.; Baccalaureate addresses; Universities and Colleges -- Administration; Administrative records; Commencement ceremonies; Tickets.; Graduation speeches; Printed ephemera.; Education, Higher -- Awards; Invitations.; Rosters.; New York University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Series I: Events, 1870, 1917-2019; 25 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 11 manuscript boxes, one half manuscript box, 1 flat-file folder, 1 card box, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 28 boxes without container profiles.; 47 audiocassettes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains planning files and print material dating from 1870 to 2019 for New York University recurring and individual events including NYU Presidential inaugurations, student orientations, Alumni activities, building groundbreaking ceremonies, NYU Sesquicentennial celebrations, faculty and freshman convocations, presentations, lectures, and Parent's Day/Weekend events. Planning files typically contain correspondence, notes, mock-ups for print items, published material, and ephemera. Series II contains ephemera for many of the events listed in this series.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Inauguration of NYU President Reverend Howard Crosby -- Program, November 17, 1870 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Honorary Degree Awards Lists and Citations, 1917-1973 (Box 46, Folder 1-6, Box 45, Folder 1-4)
  - Alumni Association / Federation -- History, Memos, Events, Ten Year Summary, Various Branches, 1925-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1-12)
  - Albert Gallatin Statue -- History, Artist Biographical Material, Related Correspondence, 1934, 1967-1996 (Box 47, Folder 1-13)
  - Meritorious Formula Sub-Committee Combinations, 1967-1978 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Convocation for Freshmen, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bobst Dedication and Gala -- NYU Present James Hester Farewell, May 30, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Health, Welfare and Benefits Committee, 1975-1984 (Box 25, Folder 5-8, 10)
  - Graduation Ceremonies Gala, May 28, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Convocation for New Students, September 11, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Tax on Gifts, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Tolbert's Convocation, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Director of Emeritus Award Past Recipients, 1976-1991 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Convocation of James Hester, April 18, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Parents of Freshmen Convocation, September 25, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee and Recommendations, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst 1978 Memorial Service -- Library Original Architectural Floor Plans, Images, and Promotional Booklet; Floorplan of Seating for Service, 1965-1977 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Arnold and Marie Schwartz Hall of Dental Sciences Dedication, September 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Service, September 13, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Service Event Building Floor Plan, September 13, 1978 (Box Shared University Archives 145, Folder 13)
  - "Pit" Day, Orientation -- Invitation, Ephemera, September 19, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Floor Plans, Space Usage for Events, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Parents Day, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Service Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Coles Sports and Recreation Center Groundbreaking, July 11, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Pit" Day Orientation, September 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square University College (WSUC) Parents Day, November 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Parents Day Convocation, Fall 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Business and Political Economy (BPA) Parents Day, December 9, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Parents Day, December 9, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dale Smith Memorial Fund -- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Parents Day, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4-7)
  - Center for Spanish Studies -- Correspondence, Newsletter, Promotional Booklet, 1979, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Original University Building, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Portraits of Former NYU Presidents and Chancellors -- Notes, Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Convocation for Endowed Chairs Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NYU Postage Stamp Transactions -- Trade Reports, Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Interdepartmental, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - General Department Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Proclamation Ceremony -- City Hall, October 13, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 25th Annual Albert Gallatin Association Reception, October 26, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Jehan El-Sadat Convocation Program, Press Release, Photographs, and Mailing Lists, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26-28)
  - Brochures, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence -- Interdepartmental, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Facilities, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Art Exhibitions, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Celebration of the Arts, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Humanities Seminars, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Named Professorships, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- General, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Finance Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Sesquicentennial Calendar, Posters, and Pin Sales, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 23-25, Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 11)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Expenses, Planning, Proposals, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 34-38)
  - Hearing on Arts and Education, March 5, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture Expenses, March 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Jose and Miguel de Capriles, April 3, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, April 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kriser Seminar, April 21, 1982 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_002 -- 7_4_003)
  - Speakers, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Groundbreaking Invitations, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Invitations, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Program, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Remarks by Dr. John Brademas, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Coles Sports and Recreation Center Dedication, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - John Brademas Inauguration Slide Images, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Parents Day, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sadat Convocation, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
  - Kriser Seminar Exp., April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kriser Presidential Seminar, April 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - List Greeks, April 22, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Livingston Papers Reception, April 22, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Orientation, April 22, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - West Springfield H.S. Visit, May 25, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Convocation Orientation, September 9, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Morse Exhibit and Terra Dinner, September 14, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nirenberg Reception and Dinner, October 6, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Dinner, October 6, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Parents Day, October 24, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Convocation Procession Reply Cards, November 1, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Convocation, November 1, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Part-time Faculty, November 19, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Broadway Opening, December 9, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Health, Welfare and Benefit Fund Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Health, Welfare, and Benefit Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Counts by School, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association / Federation -- Travel Events, 1982, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Badinter Dinner Lecture, January 22, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Varsity Basketball Press Conference, February 17, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Silverstein / Coles P.H. Dinner, March 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Announcement Press Conference and Luncheon, March 8, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Press Conference: Copyright Law, April 14, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tip O'Neill Day, April 16, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Fellows Dinner, April 21, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Valry Giscard d'Estaing Dinner, April 27, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Kriser Seminar: Joseph Califano, April 28, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_004)
  - Oxford - Cambridge Debate, Spring 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Abby Weed Grey Publication Dinner, May 9, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Up with People, June 9, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Humanities High School Reception, July 25, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Provost's Slideshow / Receptions, Summer 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Convocation for Freshmen, September 12, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Dedication of "Bobcat", September 15, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - American Jewish Congress Panel, September 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - President Eanes Visit, September 18, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Foundation Executives, September 27, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, September 28, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Convocation, October 11, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Development Campaign 1st Year Report Press Conference and Luncheon, October 11, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
  - Bobst Library 10th Anniversary, October 25, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28-29, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, November 10, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Basketball Celebration, November 26, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Abby Grey Memorial Service, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Emta Faculty Reception, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Great Teachers, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Convocation A/A Orders, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Convocation A.A. Reference, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Convocation Attendance Statistics, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - S.C.E. Fiftieth Anniversary, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Basketball Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Directors Emeriti Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Finance Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23-26, Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NYU Choral Alumni Club -- 110th and 120th Anniversaries, 1983, 1992-1995 (Box 49, Folder 10-11)
  - President Konstantinos Karamanlis Visit, April 6, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sir Steven Runciman Convocation and Law School Reception, October 18, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_005)
  - Bowshier Lecture, Reception and Dinner, October 22, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 26th Dormitory Dedication, October 24, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Picasso Exhibit Preview / Opening, October 25, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - James Burke Dinner, October 30, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Gala Dinner Dance, November 3, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Third Annual Faculty Convocation, November 14, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture -- Henry Grunwald, November 15, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_006)
  - Reverend Iakovos Convocation, November 25, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - 1984 Events (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - New Exhibits for Snow, Von Guerard, and Pres, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Report on Graduate Education in America Pub., 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Alumni Association, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Health, Welfare, and Benefit Fund Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Federation Student Relations Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Winter Celebration, March 2, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Afternoon at the Square, March 10, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYU in Albany Day, March 13, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Graphic Arts Tech. Awards, March 14, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ral Alfonsn Convocation and Honorary Degree, March 21, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Lena Horne Benefit, April 13, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, April 17, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Chancellor's Service Award Ceremony, May 6, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Italy: Festival, June 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Senior Week Breakfast, June 4, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Trustee Pre-Commencement Dinner Program, June 4, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Trustee Pre-Commencement Dinner Package, June 5, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Petrie Inaugural Lecture, October 17, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Distribution of 1983-1984 Annual Report, Spring 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - C.I.M.S. Robotics Conference, September 9 - November 1, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Convocation, September 12, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Fergus G.B. Millar Lecture, September 27, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Weiner, Kriser Professor, Event, October 3, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tisch School of the Arts 20th Anniversary and Award Dinner, October 15, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_007)
  - Shimon Peres Honorary Degree, October 21, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 26, Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Professor James Stoker Convocation, October 22, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_008)
  - Gottschalk Convocation, October 28, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_009)
  - Allen Greenberg Reception, November 12, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Morse Professorship / Kinnell Publication, November 19, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture: Diane Sawyer, November 20, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_010)
  - Forman Gymnasium Dedication, December 3, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Chancellor's Holiday Party, December 16, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Campaign Announcement Luncheon, December 17, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_011)
  - Travel Committee (Federation Committee), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Federation: Committee on Relations with the University, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Paul A. McGhee Lecture, January 13, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Puerto Rico Graduation, January 18, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Florida Alumni Event, January 26, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Edmund Muskie Visit, January 30, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Gerald Ford Visit to B.P.A., March 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Young Alumni Event, March 22, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire Commemoration 75th Anniversary, March 25, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - C.A.S.E. / Postal Rate Commission, March 27, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Inside Story: "The New Spain", March 31, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting, April 1, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - G.P.A. Marnold Lecture, April 21, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sir Harold Acton Visit, Spring 1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Between the Summits Conference, May 2, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - California Alumni Event, May 4, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, May 7, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Avery Fisher Center Dedication, May 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Leo Jaffe Theatre Dedication, May 21, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - U.A.A. Press Conference, June 25, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Chinese University Presidents, July 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Liberty Conference, July 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report Distribution, Summer 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Tiffany & Co. Anniversary, Fall 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Corazon Aquino Lecture, September 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Time Lecture: President Benigno Aquino, September 19, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Plaque, September 23, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NYU Parade, September 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Park Bench -- Painting, October 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Todman Center Dedication, October 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Henry Kissinger, December 1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Humanities Council 10th Anniversary, December 4, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Regional Alumni Activities, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Centennial, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Special Services Committee, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Recommendations, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Meritorious Service Award, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Trustees Dinner -- President John Sawhill Portrait, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - 1985-1986 Faculty Convocation (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1986-1987 Recent Alumni Event (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Washington D.C. Alumni Event, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - President Mario Soares Visit, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Florida Alumni Events, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - California Alumni Events, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Allocation Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Black Book Originals, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Board Plans and Board Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Summer Music Theater 10th Anniversary -- Program, Correspondence, 1986, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 13)